Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Course Bulletins MC.286
New York University Archives
- Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development (RG 26), 1888-2015
  - Bulletins, 1900-1921 (Volume RG26 Bulletins - Bound 1900-1921)
  - Bulletins and related materials, 1914-1916, 1922-1942 (Box 91)
    Includes the Institute of Education.
  - Bulletins, 1921-1930 (Box 92)
  - Bulletins, 1923-1934 (Box 93)
  - Bulletins, 1931-1935 (Box 94)
  - Bulletins, 1934-1939 (Box 95)
  - Bulletins, 1938-1941 (Box 96)
  - Bulletins, 1940-1946 (Box 97)
  - Bulletins, 1940-1949, 1952-1953 (Box 98)
    Includes Department of Dramatic Art (1952-1953).
  - Bulletins, 1946-1951 (Volume RG26 Bulletins - Bound 1946-1951)
  - Bulletins, 1951-1953 (Volume RG26 Bulletins - Bound 1951-1953)
  - Methods of Techniques in Social Recreation 180.298 syllabus, Spring 1954 (Box 91)
  - Bulletins, 1954-1955, 1959-1969 (Box 99)
  - Bulletins, 1955-1960 (Volume RG26 Bulletins - Bound 1955-1960)
  - Bulletins, 1960-1963 (Volume RG26 Bulletins - Bound 1960-1963)
  - Bulletins, 1963-1967 (Volume RG26 Bulletins - Bound 1963-1967)
  - Bulletins, 1969-1976 (Box 100)
  - Bulletins, 1977-1980 (Box 101)
  - Bulletins, 1980-1983 (Box 102)
  - Bulletins, 1983-1987 (Box 103)
  - Bulletins, 1987-1992 (Box 104)
  - Bulletins, 1992-1997 (Box 105)
  - Bulletins, 1996-2004 (Box 106)
  - Bulletins, 2003-2008 (Box 107)
  - Bulletins, 2008-2011 (Box 108)
  - Undergraduate Bulletins (PDFs), 2003-2014 (E-records Box - MC 286)
  - Graduate Bulletins (PDFs), 2005-2015 (E-records Box - MC 286)
- Stern School of Business (Undergraduate) (RG 27), 1900-2015
  - Bulletins, 1900-1913 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1900-1913)
  - Bulletins and Programs, 1906-1907, 1912-1916, 1920-1921, 1923-1924, 1927-1935 (Box 109)
    Includes copies of addresses delivered under the Don R. Mellett Memorial Fund for the Department of Journalism (1931-1935).
  - Bulletins, 1913-1921 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1913-1921)
  - Bulletins, 1921-1926 (Volume RG27 Bulletins Bound 1921-1926)
  - Bulletins, 1926-1933 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1926-1933)
  - Programs (2 copies), 1928-1929 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1928-1929)
  - Programs (2 copies), 1929-1930 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1929-1930)
  - Programs (2 copies), 1930-1931 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1930-1931)
  - Programs (2 copies), 1931-1932 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1931-1932)
  - Programs (2 copies), 1932-1933 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1932-1933)
  - Programs (2 copies), 1933-1934 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1933-1934)
  - Bulletins, 1933-1941 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1933-1941)
  - Programs, 1934-1935 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1934-1935)
  - Bulletins and Programs, 1934-1963 (Box 110)
  - Programs, 1935-1936 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1935-1936)
  - Programs (2 copies), 1936-1937 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1936-1937)
  - Programs (2 copies), 1937-1938 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1937-1938)
  - Programs (2 copies), 1938-1939 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1938-1939)
  - Programs (2 copies), 1939-1940 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1939-1940)
  - Programs (2 copies), 1940-1941 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1940-1941)
  - Programs (2 copies), 1941-1942 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1941-1942)
  - Bulletins, 1941-1949 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1941-1949)
  - Programs (2 copies), 1942-1943 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1942-1943)
  - Programs (2 copies), 1943-1944 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1943-1944)
  - Programs (2 copies), 1944-1945 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1944-1945)
  - Programs (2 copies), 1945-1946 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1945-1946)
  - Programs (2 copies), 1946-1947 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1946-1947)
  - Programs (2 copies), 1947-1948 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1947-1948)
  - Programs (2 copies), 1948-1949 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1948-1949)
  - Bulletins, 1949-1955 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1949-1955)
  - Bulletins, 1955-1962 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1955-1962)
  - Bulletins, 1962-1963 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1962-1963)
  - Bulletins, 1963-1967 (Volume RG27 Bulletins - Bound 1963-1967)
  - Bulletins and Programs, 1963-1972 (Box 111)
  - Bulletins and Programs, 1972-1985 (Box 112)
  - Bulletins and Programs, 1984-1998 (Box 113)
  - Bulletins and Programs, 1998-2010 (Box 114)
  - Bulletin (PDF), 2013-2015 (E-records Box - MC 286)
- Stern School of Business (Graduate) (RG 28), 1916-2016
  - Bulletins, 1916-1931 (Volume RG28 Bulletins - Bound 1916-1931)
  - Bulletins, 1918-1921, 1940-1941, 1945-1946, 1950-1951, 1952-1953, 1954-1955, 1959-1979 (Box 115)
    Includes Summer School bulletins (1959-1963).
  - Bulletins, 1931-1944 (Volume RG28 Bulletins - Bound 1931-1944)
  - Bulletins, 1945-1953 (Volume RG28 Bulletins - Bound 1945-1953)
  - Bulletins, 1955-1963 (Volume RG28 Bulletins - Bound 1955-1963)
  - Bulletins, 1963-1971 (Volume RG28 Bulletins - Bound 1963-1971)
  - Bulletins, 1972-1978 (Volume RG28 Bulletins - Bound 1972-1978)
  - Bulletins, 1979-1985 (Box 116)
  - Bulletins, 1985-1991 (Box 117)
  - Bulletins, 1993-1999, 2001-2002 (Box 118)
  - Bulletins, 2002-2005, 2008-2010 (Box 119)
  - Bulletins (PDFs), 2000-2016 (E-records Box - MC 286)
- School of Commerce, Accounts and Finance - Wall Street Division (RG 28.9), 1915-1940
  - Bulletins, 1915-1916, 1917-1919, 1920-1940 (Box 120)
- School of Retailing/Institute of Retail Management (RG 30), 1922-1978
  - Bulletins, 1922-1948 (Volume RG30 Bulletins - Bound 1922-1948)
  - Bulletins, 1948-1963 (Volume RG30 Bulletins - Bound 1948-1963)
  - Bulletins, 1919, 1922-1923, 1925-1927, 1928-1933, 1934-1941, 1955-1958 (Box 121)
    Includes proposed course of study for Training School for Teachers of Retail Selling (1919).
  - Bulletins, 1959-1978 (Box 122)
- School of Architecture and Allied Arts (RG 31), 1926-1941
  - Bulletins, 1926-1940 (Volume RG31 Bulletins - Bound 1926-1940)
  - Bulletins, 1929-1935, 1940-1941 (Box 123)
- School of Professional Studies (RG 32), 1903-2015
  Includes Extramural Divisions, Extension Divisions, and Division of General Education.
  - Bulletins, 1903-1904, 1916-1941 (Box 124)
  - Bulletins, 1934-1941, 1952-1957 (Box 125)
  - Bulletins - Course for Adults, 1950 (Volume RG32 Bulletins - Bound 1950)
  - Bulletins - Course for Adults, 1951 (Volume RG32 Bulletins - Bound 1951)
  - Bulletins - Course for Adults, 1952 (Volume RG32 Bulletins - Bound 1952)
  - Bulletins, 1958-1959, 1961-1965, 1967-1970 (Box 126)
  - Bulletins - Courses Open to the Public, 1965-1967 (Volume RG32 Bulletins - Bound 1965-1967)
  - Bulletins - Courses Open to the Public, 1967-1969 (Volume RG32 Bulletins - Bound 1967-1969)
  - Bulletins, 1971-1973 (Box 127)
  - Bulletins, 1974-1976 (Box 128)
  - Bulletins, 1977-1979 (Box 129)
  - Bulletins, 1979-1980 (Box 130)
  - Bulletins, 1981-1982 (Box 131)
  - Bulletins, 1983-1984 (Box 132)
  - Bulletins, 1984-1986 (Box 133)
  - Bulletins, 1986-1988 (Box 134)
  - Bulletins, 1988-1990 (Box 135)
  - Diploma in Bank Lending, Concentration in Credit Analysis, 1990-1991 (Box 135)
  - Bulletins, 1990-1992, 1994-1996 (Box 136)
  - Bulletins, 1992-1995 (Box 137)
  - Bulletins, 1996-1998 (Box 138)
  - Bulletins, 1998-1999 (Box 139)
  - Bulletins, 1999-2000 (Box 140)
  - Bulletins, 2000-2001 (Box 141)
  - Bulletins, 2002-2003 (Box 142)
  - Bulletins, 2003-2004 (Box 143)
  - Bulletins, 2005-2007 (Box 144)
  - Bulletins, 2007-2009 (Box 145)
  - Bulletins, 2009-2010, 2012, 2014 (Box 146)
  - Bulletins, 2015 (Box 147)
- School of Professional Studies - American Language Institute for International Students (RG 32.1), 1964-1976
  - Bulletins, 1964-1965, 1967-1971, 1974-1976 (Box 148)
- School of Professional Studies - Real Estate Institute (RG 32.3), 1970-1993
  - Bulletins, 1970-1971, 1974-1988 (Box 149)
  - Bulletins, 1988-1997, 2000-2001 (Box 150)
  - Bulletins, 1992-1993 (Box 137)
- School of Professional Studies - Paul McGhee Division (RG 32.12), 1985-2012
  - Bulletins, 1985-1992 (Box 151)
  - Bulletins, 1992-2001 (Box 152)
  - Bulletins, 2000-2012 (Box 153)
- School of Professional Studies - General Studies Program (RG 32.13), 1979-1992
  - Bulletins, 1979-1983, 1991-1992 (Box 154)
- Paterson Collegiate Center (RG 32.40), 1926-1932
  - Bulletins, 1926-1932 (Box 184)
- Newark Institute of Arts and Sciences (RG 32.41), 1915-1916
  - Announcements, 1915-1916 (Box 184)
- Westchester County Centers (RG 32.42), 1928-1931
  - Bulletins, 1928-1931 (Box 184)
- Hempstead Center (RG 32.43), 1930-1931
  - Bulletins, 1930-1931 (Box 184)
- Robert F. Wagner Graduate School of Public Service (RG 33), 1938-2011
  - Bulletins, 1938-1944, 1947-1963 (Box 155)
  - Bulletins, 1963-1982 (Box 156)
  - Bulletins, 1982-1995 (Box 157)
  - Bulletins, 1996-2011 (Box 158)
- Silver School of Social Work (RG 34), 1960-2014
  - Bulletins, 1960-1986 (Box 159)
  - Bulletins, 1986-2010 (Box 160)
  - Bulletin (PDF), 2013-2014 (E-records Box - MC 286)
- Tisch School of the Arts (RG 35), 1986-2015
  - Bulletins, 1966-1984 (Box 161)
  - Bulletins, 1983-1992 (Box 162)
  - Bulletins, 1991-2003 (Box 163)
  - Bulletins, 2003-2013 (Box 164)
  - Bulletins (PDFs), 2009-2011, 2013-2015 (E-records Box - MC 286)
- Gallatin School of Individualized Study (RG 36), 1981-2012
  - Bulletins, 1981-1998 (Box 165)
  - Bulletins, 1998-2005 (Box 166)
  - Bulletins, 2006-2010 (Box 167)
  - Bulletins (PDFs), 2009-2012 (E-records Box - MC 286)
- Deutsches Haus (RG 37.3), 1977-1995
  - German language courses, 1977, 1981-1982, 1987-1992, 1995 (Box 168)
- Center for International Studies (RG 37.5), 1965-1971
  - Bulletins, 1965-1971 (Box 169)
- Institute for Hebrew and Judaic Studies (RG 37.8), 1963-1972
  - Bulletins, 1963-1972 (Box 170)
- Center for Near Eastern Studies (RG 37.14), 1987-1990
  - Bulletins, 1987-1990 (Box 170)
- Nassau College-Hofstra Memorial (RG 37.32), 1934-1939
  - Bulletins, 1934-1939 (Box 171)
- Tandon School of Engineering (RG 48), 1981-2016
  Includes Polytechnic Institute of New York materials.
  - Bulletins, 2009-2011 (Box 171)
  - Bulletins (PDFs), 1981-1990, 1992-1995, 1999-2016 (E-records Box - MC 286)
- NYU Abu Dhabi (RG 49), 2015-2016
  - Bulletin (PDF), 2015-2016 (E-records Box - MC 286)
- NYU Shanghai (RG 50), 2013-2016
  - Bulletins (PDFs), 2013-2016 (E-records Box - MC 286)
- Non-course catalog publications
  - The Charter and the Statutes Defining the Organization and Government of New York University, 1909 (Box 179)
  - Tercentenary Accouncements 1609-1909 "Three Epochs in Education in New York City", June 1909 (Box 179)
  - The Alumni Electorate Secretary's Report, June 1910 (Box 179)
  - NYU Its Organization and Equipment, June 1911 (Box 179)
  - Address at the Opening of the Academic Year by Elmer Ellsworth Brown, September 1915 (Box 179)
  - The Charter and the Statutes Defining the Organization and Government of New York University, 1915 (Box 179)
  - Extracts from the Rules of the College of Arts and Pure Science and School of Applied Arts, June 1917 (Box 179)
  - Activities in Relation to the War, January 1918 (Box 179)
  - Roll of Honor, July 1918 (Box 179)
  - Announcement of Courses Opening on January First and February First, with Special Reference to the Needs o Soldiers and Sailors Recently Released from Service, December 1918 (Box 179)
  - General Information booklets, 1927-1936 (Box 179)
  - University Bibliography, 1931-1935 (Box 179)
  - A List of Reference Books with Descriptive Notes for Freshmen, 1933, 1935 (Box 179)
  - Bulletin: University Bibliography, 1950 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1950)